# Caden Lee



CadenCLee@protonmail.com



linkedin.com/in/caden-lee-b3aab917a



306 260 7836



https://www.cadenlee.net

## Summary

A high-school graduate with experience cashiering at a local business. Has experience with customer service, stocking shelves, cleaning store, and operating store alone when the manager is away.

Is skilled in file management and note taking, and can offer rudimentary tech support. Took First-Aid and WHIMS courses during high school.

## **Experience**



## Cashier

Young Food Store

Nov 2022 - Present (10 months)

I stock shelves whenever a new shipment comes in, clean the floors and windows regularly, and run the till when there are customers.

When my boss is away, I open, close, and operate the store alone.

Once a week I also setup that week's sales and setup the sale tags.

## Intern

#### LANGDON CHAMBER OF COMMERCE

Aug 2022 - Sep 2022 (2 months)

I researched, designed, and implemented a file management scheme for LDCC

I sorted and organized disparate files with arbitrary file-names

I created a mock file-system using only folders and shortcuts before I even began moving or renaming

I created file-naming conventions as needed and renamed files as appropriate.

### **Education**



## NorQuest College

**ACT! Certificate Program** 2022 - 2022



## Winston High School

High School Diploma 2020 - 2021

#### **Skills**

Summarizing Information • Easily Adaptable • Time Management • Cashiering • Sanitation • English Copy Editing
Customer Service
Floor Cleaning
Note Taking